cae.com 2019-06-05

# Privacy Policy | CAE

**Internet Privacy Statement**

**Introduction  **

At CAE, your privacy is important to us. CAE is committed to providing visitors with websites that respect their privacy. This statement sets out our privacy practices with respect to the collection, use and disclosure of personal data on this Website.

This Website may contain links that take you to websites of third parties. This privacy statement does not extend to the data collection practices of third parties and CAE does not assume any responsibility for the privacy practices, policies or actions of third parties. You should read the individual privacy policies and/or legal notices of such sites and make an informed decision as to whether or not you wish to use these sites based on their privacy practices.

**Personal data**

Personal data means data or information about an identifiable person, recorded in any form. When you interact with us on our Website, you may be asked to provide and disclose, on a voluntary basis (consent), your name, e-mail address, mailing address, telephone number and other similar contact information, as the case may be. Visitors of this Website may provide and disclose personal data to us in using certain features of our Website, like our contact form or our newsletter service. The personal data CAE processes for providing such features are limited to name and contact information. This Website may also provide you access to specific webpages for certain services that require you to register and provide other or additional personal data. A separate privacy policy will in that case apply and will be shown to you when accessing that page.

**Processing and purpose of use**

CAE processes your personal data in order to provide you with the requested services or enable you to use certain features of the Website. The services requested by you may contain marketing information. CAE will not sell or make commercially available any personal data that you provide through this Website without your permission. 

**Disclosure of personal data**

If you submit an inquiry through this Website, any personal data you might submit at that time will only be used by employees, representatives or agents of CAE, its affiliates or third parties who need to have access to it in order to respond to your inquiry, to provide the requested services, for proper administration (including storage in the cloud) or for marketing purposes.

CAE will only share your personal data with third parties or affiliates, if those third parties or affiliates are established in a country which is recognized as providing an adequate data protection level or if such entity has signed a contract with CAE for processing personal data in compliance with applicable data protection laws. 

CAE may disclose personal data to respond to legal requirements, enforce its corporate policies, respond to claims or protect anyone's vital interests. Disclosure will be in accordance with the applicable data protection laws.

**Protection of personal data**

CAE is committed to ensuring that your personal data is stored securely and only accessible by authorized persons. Your personal data will only be transferred to other parties in accordance with this Privacy Statement, following the implementation of appropriate technical and organizational measures in compliance with applicable data protection laws. Nonetheless there are third parties that may unlawfully try to access systems or intercept transmissions or communications containing personal data. CAE continuously uses its reasonable efforts in line with industry standards to protect your personal data but cannot absolutely guarantee that such unlawful actions will not occur. Consequently, CAE bears no liability for the use that may be made of the information by any third party. CAE has in place an adequate data breach response plan. 

**Storage duration**

CAE will only store your personal data for the duration necessary for providing you with the requested services or features of the Website and in a manner permitted by applicable laws. 

**Rights of data subjects  **

You - as the individual whose personal data CAE processes - have the right to withdraw your consent to CAE’s processing of your personal data at any time, which results in the immediate termination of the processing without affecting the lawfulness of processing based on consent before your withdrawal and, if necessary, the deletion of all personal data. You have the right to request access to your personal data held by CAE, request (e.g. for transfer to another IT environment) for a copy of such personal data, and to request to update or correct it. You also have the right to object to the processing of your personal data by CAE, to request CAE to restrict its processing or to request to erase it. 

If you would like to exercise any of the above rights, please advise CAE by sending us an email at: _[dataprotection@cae.com](mailto:dataprotection@cae.com) _.  We will take reasonable steps to respond to your request in a timely fashion and in accordance with applicable data protection laws. 

If you believe that the processing of your personal data by CAE is not compliant with applicable data protection laws or if CAE does not respond to your requests in a timely or adequate manner, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the competent authority for the protection of personal data, in accordance with applicable data protection laws.

**Contact and further information**

Contact details of CAE Corporate Headquarters

CAE Inc.

8585 Cote-de-Liesse

Saint-Laurent, Québec

H4T 1G6 Canada

Telephone: +1-514-341-6780

If you have any comments, questions or complaints regarding CAE's Privacy Statement or practices, please contact us by sending an email to [_dataprotection@cae.com_](mailto:dataprotection@cae.com). 

**General information**

CAE reserves the right to change this Privacy Statement as it sees fit and without prior notice. However, we will ensure that any change to this Statement is in compliance with applicable data protection laws and posted on this Web site. We encourage you to refer back to this Privacy Statement regularly.

Please note that both the English and French versions of CAE's Privacy Statement have equal legal value.

Last revision: January 17, 2019.
